That this couple let's see it is okay
this is Sahitya and this is Sahil's Shamim who
loves Jon very much and does Sahil
know how obscene ji welcome to our
channel thank you it is quite simple you are
5 minutes away from your house and for half an hour you do
not contact your family if
you are at home then you played one crore in Amazon my
providence so are you also
ready to take the challenge absolutely free I am
not able to pick up their calls and then the conversation happens on reaching home
what is the problem 840 on the search bar absolutely
I cannot believe that you are going to
give me one crore rupees for this it is a
good thing expenses have increased anyway do this
my only thing is that we will give this cream to their life
and we will see the worries of your family how they wait for you let's see this
my wife always says that it is a
thing to be worried about and not to be worried that
mom and dad had promised that they will take us to
Mexico oh
one good thing you told dad that
you will really tell him take it and when dad comes he will
help you with your  No problem, I will get it done tomorrow
morning. Please do it. Please do it. I
called Ajay two or three times for the baby wise oil on Amazon but he was not picking up the phone. I had some work with him. I have his
mobile number. Let's
call
Ajay. Ajay said he had a
tumor yesterday morning. He is
not picking up the phone. I
tried to order your medicine.
Now, hello. Today I was standing for a while, then
Ajay said,
Lord of medicines, 5000
5000 Madam, I have a
question.
How will it work right now? I closed the shop and
came home.
[Music] Please do it.
Ajay did
not pick up my call. I forgot to take care of it.
Now I should withdraw from the ATM. She was going
out last night, which is not why she is fighting.
Modern and why are you fighting in such tension,
but by then she is getting so much from all over Orissa,
Hindustan, Swar
Ma is not here.
Picture of all
these people, call your friend. You
can get a leave.
[Music]
I will call the construction of my station and bring him.
Why are you calling Verma ji,
his job is to increase your tension right now.
When did you last talk to Sahil?
Okay, I will bring it to Sahil's office.
I have
emptied the MP3 and you should listen to it. Arth was robbed, then go and
sleep. Now
I am coming to Sahil's office and check it out.
If no one knows, he is 12 years old. Also,
I think we should take the help of the police. The
government is right. Where was that company Raghavendra Chauhan
kept? They are taking him out.
He is out of reach. It happened, let's
go to the police station. Okay, then
comment on
what happened. You can make as many calls as you want and yes,
I will die trying to find out the truth.
And if you never realize
that your family is your responsibility, even then the
answer will not be with them.